《打工姐妹花》前情提要
Previously on 2 Broke Girls...
台风正朝着威廉斯堡迎头而来
The hurricane is headed right for Williamsburg.
街上帽子被吹得满天飞
Fedoras are blowing down the streets,
精酿啤酒洒得满地都是
craft beers are spilling everywhere,
独立音乐乐团练习取消
and indie bands are cancelling practice.
这就是为什么兰迪还没来
This explains why Randy isn't here yet.
他估计是被困暴风雨里了
He's probably stuck in the storm.
他不接 直接转去语音信箱了
He's not answering and it's going straight to voicemail.
他很可能屏蔽你电话了
He probably blocked you.
我们真的彻底分手了
We're really broken up.
先去抱抱我们的甜品吧
Let's go hug our dessert bar.
它一定吓坏了
It was probably so scared.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max.
我们的甜品酒吧就这么毁了
Our dessert bar is destroyed.
看来我们是时候该面对现实了
I think we have to finally admit it to ourselves.
我们就是衰神
Ugh, we're cursed.
老天爷绝对跟我有仇
Yeah, this is personal.
别这样 我一年级时那个吉普赛人
Come on, when that gypsy pointed at me in first grade
对着我念"大[罩]杯咒" 那才叫诅咒
and said, "Biggus Boobus," that was a curse.
我们肯定不是唯一一家
I'm sure we weren't the only business
台风受灾户
that was ruined by the storm.
我们才没有被衰神附身
We're not cursed.
现在还开始有刺痛感了
Yeah, now it's starting to burn.
我选择将这场灾难当做一个启示
Well, I am choosing to take this disaster as a sign.
而且我们又不是没保保险
It's not like we don't have insurance.
在他们重建这里的时候
And while they're rebuilding this place,
我要去给兰迪惊喜 重建我们感情
I'm gonna go surprise Randy and try to rebuild us.
看出这关联了吗
You see the parallels?
你懂 你肯定听懂了
You get it. She gets it.
姑娘们 你们听说了吗
Girls, did you hear?
整个区域只有一家商户
Turns out only one business in the entire area
受风灾影响
was affected by the storm.
真好奇是哪家...
I wonder which one...
这事就先归类为"之后再说的事"吧
File this under "Story For Another Time"?
污中生奶变变变
Biggus Boobus!
老娘真是服了
Ugh, I don't believe this!
所有的机场停飞 仿佛我的心情般
All the airports are more shut down
大吃"闭门羹"
than I am emotionally.
厄尔 你搜到没停摆的大巴或火车了吗
Earl, have you had any luck with any busses or trains?
在查了
I'm on it.
我该按哪个按钮才会有网
What button do I push for the Internet?
我刚跟保险公司通完电话
I just talked to the insurance company.
他们会赔偿所有的损失
They're gonna pay for all our repairs.
还多给了我们一点额外补贴
And they gave me some extra money
因为我跟他们说我们俩是孕妇
'cause I told them we were pregnant.
能先关注一下我怎么去洛城这件事吗
Can we please focus on how I'm gonna get to L.A.?
我明明不要脸又有广为流传的性爱影带
I have low self-esteem and a well-viewed sex tape.
我人早该在那里才对啊
I should be there already!
麦克斯 我尽量说得不伤你心
Max, I'm gonna try to put this delicately.
但你现在就像个疯狂变态跟踪狂
You're acting like a cray-cray psycho stalker.
我才不是跟踪狂
I am not a stalker.
我都是被人家跟踪的那个
I'm the one that gets stalked.
说到跟踪狂 我应该通知一下盖瑞
That reminds me, I should probably tell Gary
我要出远门
I'm going out of town.
他能不知道吗
Oh, he knows.
他今早在家门口脚踏垫拉了祝一路平安屎
He left a bon voyage dookie on our welcome mat this morning.
但贺卡挺贴心的啊
But the card was sweet.
那我作为你的闺蜜
Well, then as your best friend,
我要陪你去 确保你平平安安
I am going with you to make sure you're okay.
兰迪给过我航空公司礼券
You know, Randy did give me an airline voucher
就是我第一次毁了感情那会给的
when I ruined our relationship the first time.
我估计可以拿去换到两张票
I could probably get two tickets for that,
这样我就有地方放脚了
so I could put my feet up.
或者也可以让你跟来啦
Or I guess you could come.
如果我是你跟踪任务的帮手
If I'm the wing-lady on your stalking mission,
那这我要宣布这次是度假之旅啦
I'm gonna go ahead and call this a vacation.
好可悲啊
Wow, that's sad.
好啦 我差不多要上去网啦
All right, I'm almost on the Internet.
有人知道我的解屏密码吗
Does anybody know my password?
是"Earl"[厄尔]
It's "Earl."
没错 用的是我第一只狗的名字
Oh, right, my first dog's name.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我跟芭芭拉的一个小伙伴
I just got in a fight with one of Barbara's friends
在宜家球池里吵起来了
in the IKEA ball pit.
你想带宜家肉球丸子进球池
Yeah, if you're gonna bring meatballs in there,
那就得带够给所有人都能吃的份
you gotta bring some for everybody.
球池里的肉球丸子再多也不嫌多啊
Yeah, there's never enough meatballs in a ball pit.
厄尔 我们去洛杉矶的事怎么样了
Earl, how we doing on our trip to L.A.?
租车店的车全租出去了
Well, the rental cars are rented out,
火车停摆 航班停飞到周二
trains are down, and no flights till Tuesday.
我还收到了表情包发来的短信 谁是表情包
And I got a message from emoji. Who's emoji?
你们何不公路旅行开车过去
Hey, why don't you two just road trip it?
后车厢带着一冷却箱的啤酒
You know, throw a cooler of beer
以及手撕猪肉条 然后就头也不回上路
with pulled pork in the trunk and just go, baby.
要不是我有个要喂奶的大娃
I would do the same if I didn't have
我也想这样去旅行
that giant breastfeeding baby.
我说的是奥列格
I'm talking about Oleg.
我能建议你们开我卖给阿憨的丰田小车吗
May I suggest the Toyota Yaris I sold to Han?
它很省油
It's efficient on gas,
而且后车厢无法从车里打开呢
and the trunk can't be unlocked from the inside.
你们别想开我的车
Oh, no! You're not taking my car.
这次轮到我载我的缝花被子俱乐部
It's my turn to drive my quilting group
去农贸市场了
to the farmers' market.
阿憨 我们可以来硬的
Han, we can do this the hard way
就是你不给我钥匙 我把你内裤拉到你头上
where you don't give me the keys and I give you a wedgie,
或是你乖乖配合 交出车钥匙
or the easy way where you do give me the keys
我拉你内裤套头时下手轻点
and I give you a slightly less intense wedgie.
车钥匙就在我办公室里 但你别想...
The keys are in my office, but you're not...
靠 我说溜嘴了
Oh, dear, I've said too much.
你猜这场龙争鼠斗谁会赢
Who do you see winning this one?
我先告诉你 麦克斯为了防这种情况
And you should know, Max keeps a pocket full of sand
永远带了一口袋的沙子
for these kinda things.
叮当到手 小婊子们
Jingle-jangle, bitches!
就你刚才的行为 我就该炒了你
You should be fired for what happened back there.
猴子偷桃是禁止的
Bathing suit areas are off limits.
行吧 开我的车去
Fine, use my car,
但必须是我来驾驶
but I'm going to be driving it.
我要跟你去
I'm coming with you.
我好不容易才把短腿油门辅助器调到位
I finally got the gas pedal extension where I like it.
那谁来管餐厅啊
But who's gonna run the diner?
对了 我曾经营过一家挺成功的"小保健"
FYI, I managed a pretty successful jerk shack for years.
恶心鬼奥列格
Ew, Oleg.
干嘛啦 你别想歪好吗
What? Get your mind out of the gutter.
我们卖牙买加风味鸡肉
We sold Jamaican-style chicken.
来给我们的小保健打掩护
As a front for full-release massages.
问一下 我第一只狗的名字叫啥来着
Y'all, what was my first dog's name again?
-厄尔 -干嘛
- Earl. - What?
看来管店人选只有奥列格跟厄尔了
I guess my only options here are Oleg and Earl.
哎妈 一时之选 个个要命啊
Woof, real Murderers' Row.
那服务员怎么办
Who are you gonna have waitress?
他们还得能跟得上
'Cause you know they'll have to match
由我搭档与我亲自设下的超超低标准呢
the extremely low bar set by my associate and myself.
能让我当吗
Oh, can I do it?
我开什么玩笑呢
Oh, who am I kidding?
我当然可以
Or course I can!
我曾经在波头鹰餐厅当过服务员
I actually used to be a waitress at Pooters.
你是说猫头鹰餐厅吗
You mean Hooters?
不 我那个是波兰版的
No, it was Poland's version.
我们那里女服务员下半身不穿
Yeah, all the waitresses were bottomless.
那希望你们那里戴了很多"发网"啊
I'm hoping there were a lot of hairnets involved.
按理说是该这样...
Oh, you'd think so.
阿憨 我本来想说你开车像老太婆
Han, I'd say you drive like a little old lady,
但已经三个老太婆超我们车了
but three of them just passed us.
我开车载我的毒舌朋友尼尔去医院吸水泡
I had more fun driving my bitchy friend Neil
都没载你们闹心
to get his blisters drained.
所以现在有啥计划了没
Also, what's the strategy here?
都已经开了好几小时车了
We've been driving for hours.
等我们找到没关闭的机场
Well, once we find an open airport,
我们就飞去洛城 麦克斯就给兰迪个惊喜
we'll fly to L.A., where Max will surprise Randy,
然后她就用舌头狂甩兰迪
and she'll be all, "Ahhh,"
然后兰迪也跟她...
and he'll be all, "Ahhh."
首先 兰迪学得太像
First of all, great Randy impression.
差点就忍不住给你来点...
I almost gave you a little "Wahhh""
你们俩的事先计划
You girls have less of a game plan
比《美国恐怖故事》任何一季的剧情还少
than any season of American Horror Story.
而且谁需要什么计划啊
Well, who really needs a game plan anyway?
我现在可是在度假啊
I'm on vacation, baby.
你看 说出来都不会掉泪了
See? Didn't even tear up that time.
这些零食都是咋回事
What's with these snacks?
蔬菜干
Vegetables?
你又再吃什么兔子瘦身饮食了吗
Are you on that bunny diet again?
不是 而且我吃了还胖了呢
No, I gained weight on that somehow.
阿憨 你好多摇滚乐团咕咕玩偶的盘啊
Han, there's a lot of Goo Goo Dolls here.
还有咕咕偶之现场咕
GGD-Live Goo. Wow.
你凭啥要听一个
I'm taking music criticism
跳梁小丑的脑残粉批评我的音乐口味啊
from a proud member of the Juggalo nation?
给我片白萝卜干
Hand me a radish.
白萝卜是要嚼多久才正常啊
I mean, how long are you supposed to chew a radish?
一辈子吗
Forever?
我能给你们介绍个小景点
Can I interest anyone in a side trip
去松泉谷玩吗
to Pine Creek Gorge?
如果你们喜欢大峡谷
If you love the Grand Canyon,
你们也会觉得这宾州小峡谷也还行
you'll think Pine Creek Gorge is pretty good.
我勒个大去
Oh, my seasonal gourd.
看看兰迪的新快拍
Look at Randy's Snapchat story.
连律师都有自己的休息拖车
they even got the lawyer is own trailer.
不对 不是自己的
Oh! Scratch that.
我还跟一只非常大的蝎子分享
I'm sharing it with a very large scorpion.
你现在连蝎子的醋也吃了吗
You're jealous of a scorpion now?
你沦落到这境地啦
That's where we're at?
不是
No!
是兰迪肩膀上的手指
There's a finger on Randy's shoulder.
是女人的手指
A woman's finger.
做过指甲 没有婚戒
Manicured nail, no wedding ring.
她哪来的狗胆
How dare she?
松泉谷你们是要去还是不去呢
Yea nor nay on Pine Creek Gorge?
再三英里就到出口了
The exit's in three miles,
我该开始换道了
and I should start changing lanes.
所以是或许吗
So that's a maybe?
我得查出这只贱爪子
I gotta finger this out!
为什么影片不能放大啊
Ugh, why can't you zoom in on a video?
我知道肯定有这技术了
I know we have the technology.
这技术在
It was used against me
猎具用品店对麦克斯·布莱克一案中害过我
in the case of Bass Pro Shops versus Max Black.
我的无花果里好像有个核
Ugh, I think there's a pit in my fig.
那是梅子干
That's a prune,
我能建议你别太猴急吗
and I'd pace yourself.
卡洛琳 你能打去餐厅 看看情况吗
Caroline, could you call the diner and check in?
一整天打过去都是答录机
I've been getting the machine all day,
我得确定奥列格没在店里拍黄片
and I gotta make sure Oleg isn't shooting a porno there.
他没筹到足够资金
Oh, he didn't get the funding.
他的黄筹网项目没凑够钱
His Kinkstarter campaign fizzled out.
好啦 电话拔掉了
There, the phone is unplugged.
现在看你怎么打给警察 第二桌
Good luck calling the police now, table two.
你拔掉电话的速度
Wow, you unplugged that phone
比我们拔掉我阿姨的呼吸维持器还快
faster than we unplugged my Aunt Esther.
她可讨人厌了
She was a mean lady.
苏菲 准备好重新踏进职场了吗
Sophie, ready to re-enter the workforce?
我准备好啦
I'm ready.
问题应该是 你们准备好了吗
The question is, are you ready?
答案是还没 我还没准备好
And the answer is no, I am not.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
能帮你点单吗
Can I take your order?
小姐 是气泡水还是普通水
Miss, sparkling or still?
味道如何啊
How's everything tasting?
《MMMBop》 - Hanson
真希望你们俩能赢《美国偶像》冠军
I wish you guys would win American Idol
这样就再也不用听到你们俩唱歌了
so I'd never have to hear from you ever again.
别这样嘛 麦克斯 你听嘛
Oh, come on, Max. Listen up.
公路旅行如果不合唱一下还算个什么
What's a road trip without a sing-along?
还算可以忍受啊
I don't know, tolerable.
现在来谈谈大家都在意的事情
Now let's talk about something everyone's interested in.
我截屏了兰迪的影片
I screen-grabbed Randy's video,
这样我就能放大了
which enabled me to zoom in.
而在我放大的时候 我意识到了
And upon zooming, I realized that...
你在发疯吗
You're going crazy?
麦克斯 说真的 或许我们该回家了
Max, seriously, maybe we should go back home.
兰迪都拉黑你了
Randy blocked you.
他的人生中出现新"手指"也不意外啊
You have to expect there might be a new finger in his life.
我才没有发疯
I am not going crazy.
我也只不过是随便在网上搜搜
I'm merely scouring the World Wide Web
兰迪照片里@过的所有女性朋友
for female friends of Randy who are tagged in a photo of him
然后把她们的食指截图出来
with their index fingers cropped out.
这样才能把两张截图放在一起
That way I can piece the two photos together
像拼拼图一样找出我应得的答案
jigsaw style to get the answers I deserve,
天啊 我想我好像精神崩溃了
and oh, my God, I think I'm having a breakdown.
她不是唯一一个"崩溃"的
She's not the only one.
请告诉我是吃了助排便梅子的卡洛琳放屁
Please tell me that was Caroline's prunes kicking in.
真不敢相信我们在荒郊野外抛锚了
I can't believe we're broken down in the middle of nowhere.
阿曼达·诺克斯的假期都比我们强
Amanda Knox had a better vacation than this.
我们该开始走起了 把行李箱留在这里吧
We have to start walking. Leave that suitcase here.
你都带了什么行李啊
What did you pack in there,
你其中一个又臭又长的趣闻故事吗
one of your long-winded anecdotes?
其实还真是个有趣的故事
Funny story actually.
我当时在看要带哪件毛衣
I was going through my sweaters,
我想起来我在14岁的时候
and I realized that when I was 14...
先等下...辈子在说吧
Hold that thought forever.
想找出手指 就得用手指
Now you wanna find a finger, you gotta use a finger.
麦克斯 不行 不能搭便车
Max, no! We can't hitchhike.
万一坐到变态杀人狂的车怎么办
What if some psycho picks us up?
你想想 谁不会想要剥下我这层皮来穿
Really, who wouldn't want to wear this skin?
我觉得问题应该是出在变速箱
I think the problem is the transmission.
这车没有
There is none.
我上学那会 整天都搭便车啊
I hitchhiked all the time in school.
从没发生过什么坏事
Nothing bad ever happened.
虽然的确被一个男人锁在小屋里一年过
I did spend a year locked in a guy's shed once,
但那是我们共同的决定
but that was mutual.
我要对你说我对我毕业舞伴说过的话
I'll tell you what I told my prom date,
把你的手指拿开
put that finger away.
你的当年舞伴不是基佬吗
I thought your prom date was gay.
是啊 他当年一直这样
He was. He was doing a lot of this.
太棒了 车窗贴了膜
Oh, good, tinted windows
让您拥有更隐秘私人的谋杀体验
for a more private murdering experience.
这东西冒的烟 比我奶奶宾果冠军赛时
Um, this thing is smoking more than my grandma
焦虑抽的烟还多
at the Bingo finals.
姑娘们卡在这了吗
You girls stuck?
我觉得停滞不前比较适合我们
I think "stagnant" is a better word for us.
叫我贝姬 乌溜溜秀发的贝姬
Name's Becky. With the good hair.
需要搭便车吗
Y'all need a ride?
谢谢 我要去西部 走长征路的风格
Thanks. We're going west, Fievel style.
如果你能带我们到未关闭的机场
If you could take us somewhere with outgoing flights.
你要的话 我开车也行
I can drive if you want.
我曾经帮一个哥伦比亚的运毒....
I used to do it for a Colombian drug lor...
字幕
Frito-Lay.
我可以载你们到密苏里
I can get you all the way to Missouri,
街头暴力与美国绝大多数
home to street violence and a large percentage
止痛药上瘾之都
of America's OxyContin epidemic.
太好了 麦克斯 那里都是你的同类啊
Great, and, Max, at least you'll know people.
太好了 有便车搭 那台车死到
Oh, good, we got a ride, 'cause that car is deader
比朱莉皮特夫妇感恩节席间还死气沉沉
than the conversation at the Jolie-Pitt Thanksgiving this year.
不好意思 你们姑娘们能上车
Oh, sorry, you girls can come,
但我才不让奇怪男人上我车
but I don't let strange men into my cab.
我可以为他担保 他不是男人
Oh, I can vouch for Han. He's not a man.
没事的 两位 你们先行出发吧
It's okay, girls. Go ahead without me.
我在这等保险公司来拖车就行
I'll just call AAA.
那太好啦 再见 拜拜
Cool. Later, hater.
等等
Wait!
你们真的一走了之啊
You're really leaving?
什么人会把别人就这么丢在
Who leaves someone on the side of the road
荒郊野岭的路边啊
in the middle of nowhere?
你们不是人
You're not people!
不好意思 小姐
Excuse me, Miss?
别又是你啊
Oh, not you again.
听我说 别吃这个
Listen, don't eat this.
我点了牛排 而这是脏抹布
I ordered a steak, and this is a dirty washcloth.
想我去帮你热一下吗
You want me to heat it up?
为什么总是我在帮你拿东西来啊
I mean, why am I always getting you stuff?
你这人怎么不懂知恩图报 礼尚往来呢
How come you're not scratching my back?
看到我教训他一顿了没
See how I told him off?
就像麦克斯平常那样 对吧 姐妹
You know, just like Max does, right girl?
你干嘛叫我姐妹
Why are you calling me girl?
说你是个女人啊
I'm calling you a woman.
就像她们叫阿憨那样
You like, like the girls do with Han,
可他就会乖乖听
only he takes it.
我没想过会这样
I mean, I wasn't expecting all this.
我也没有啊
Well, neither was I.
现在本来应该是我午睡时间
This is supposed to be my nap time.
这就是我的假期
This is my vacation.
我的真实生活就是这么惨
That's how bad my real life is.
我在试图跟我前男友和好
And I'm trying to get back with my ex.
他手机把我拉黑了 而我跟那个
He blocked me on his phone, and I am one diaper away
绑架过人的女太空人只差一件尿布了
from being that crazy lady astronaut.
我就从来没有过对人掏心掏肺的勇气
I never had the courage of putting myself out there.
不切实际地来说
I mean, romantically speaking.
我当年还是杀了本拉登的海豹突击队队员呢
I was on the Seal Team that killed Bin Laden.
不知道了
I don't know.
或许我的外表很坚强
I may look tough on the outside,
但其实底下还是个胆小的小女孩
but underneath it all is a scared little girl
以及无数的自制刺青
and a lot of homemade tattoos.
你一看就有很好的判断力
Well, you clearly have good judgment.
你看看这个影片 告诉我这手指
Take a look at this video and tell me if this finger
像不像进过我男朋友的嘴
looks like it's been in my boyfriend's mouth.
等等 我拿一下我的眼镜
Hold on, let me grab my glasses!
贝姬 你要选好一条道开吗
Whoa, Becks! You wanna pick a lane?
我们现在一台车占了三条道
We're currently in all three.
别干扰她看影片
Don't distract her from the video.
我喜欢
Oh, I like this.
少废话了 快亮出你的翘臀 小白男
Enough talking. Show us your ass, white boy.
对不起
So sorry.
我不知道喇叭会这么大声
I didn't know the horn would be so loud,
但你能不能让开点
but could you scooch?
不是我在开车吗
Ooh, I wasn't driving?
天啊 当特种兵真是把我都当神经病了
Man, being a Seal really messed with my head.
我也不知道我怎么现在才想起来
I don't know why I didn't think of this before,
但是我的朋友邋遢乔有一台单引擎飞机
but my friend, Sloppy Joe, has a one-engine plane.
他或许有办法载你们飞去洛杉矶
He might be able to fly y'all all the way to L.A.
抱歉 你说什么
I'm sorry, what?
牛肉酱三明治[邋遢乔]开飞机载我们吗
A messy sandwich is gonna fly us to L.A.?
好吧
Okay.
邋遢哥是我高中暗恋对象
Sloppy was an old high school crush
我从来没勇气跟他告白过
I never had the guts to go for.
他当年可是传奇人物
Man was a legend there.
他高三读了9年呢
He was a senior for nine years.
谢谢你啊 乌溜溜秀发的贝姬
Thanks, Becky With the Good Hair.
你会找到真爱的 我确定
And you'll find someone, I'm sure.
你勇敢追爱就行了
You just gotta go for it.
她也一直这么对我说
That's what she keeps telling me.
对你是客套 她是真的会找到的
I know, but she will.
我们好像还没正式自我介绍 邋遢乔
I don't think we've formally met, Sloppy Joe.
我叫卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
到时候我们的死讯将会一起被报导
They'll be reporting our deaths together.
我不会跟你们一起的
You're on your own there.
我五年前就被人报导去世了
They reported mine five years ago.
我们坐的是幽灵飞机吗 太屌了
We're on a ghost plane? Awesome!
好奇一问 机上会有餐饮服务吗
Just curious, will there be a beverage service?
想来两口我的啤酒吗
You want some of my beer?
不用了 大半瓶都撒我身上了
That's all right, you already spilled most of it on me.
所以人家才说他邋遢啊
I bet that's why they call him Sloppy.
不 我的落地是一塌糊涂才对
Nope, my landings are a mess.
卡洛琳 要往好的方面想嘛
Caroline, look at the bright side.
怎么想 所有指示灯都坏了
How? None of the lights work.
我们正在去洛杉矶的路上
We're on our way to L.A.,
而邋遢哥收了兰迪的礼券当报酬
and Sloppy took Randy's voucher as payment.
再用礼券卷了一管大麻
And then rolled a nice, fat joint with it.
这还用说
You bet I did.
穿越雷劫
Ride the lightning!
你们也叫
Do it back.
让我也听听你们这么叫唤
Let me hear you say, "Yee-haw!"
我很庆幸你找到我了
I'm just glad you found me.
我差点就要去搭个小屋过夜了
I was about to build a hut for the night.
你不是说你不接陌生男人的吗
I thought you said you didn't pick up strange men.
的确是啊
I didn't.
但我的新朋友说服我要勇于尝试
Until a new friend convinced me I gotta take a chance.
这台老东西能多快啊
How fast can this old rig go?
这"老东西"能整晚不用停
This old rig can go all night, baby.
完全答非所问
Doesn't answer my question at all,
不过既然如此 那就来吧
but let's do the damn thing.
这趟旅程比我想象中还颠簸啊
This flight's a lot bumpier than I thought it was gonna be.
说到颠簸
Speaking of bumps,
你们那里有没有一"颠"白粉
y'all don't have any blow, do you?
这趟旅程现在最需要的
Yeah, that's what this flight needs,
就是一个更神经兮兮的机长了
a more jittery pilot.
兰迪又贴了新的影片
Randy just posted a new video.
缓冲快一点啊
Eh, buffer faster!
你在这上面有信号吗
Ugh, do you get any bars up here?
我如果有信号就不用问你们有没有白粉了
If I did, I wouldn't be asking you for cocaine.
没关系 不需要等信号了
Never mind, don't need it.
我们要下去了
We're going down.
下去 我最不喜欢听人这么说了
Going down? My least favorite expression.
我现在又更讨厌这词了
And now I hate it even more.
至少这版本的"下去"
At least in this version of going down
完事后不需要抱抱啊
you don't have to spoon afterwards.
天啊
Oh, my God!
卡洛琳 天大好消息
Caroline, amazing news.
你找到降落伞了吗
You found parachutes?
或者是飞机断掉的那节机翼
Or that part of the wing that tore away?
不是的 我们早死定了
Ha, oh, no, we're goners.
但乌云背后有一道幸福线
But Silver Linings Playbook,
那根手指是兰迪妈妈的
that finger belonged to Randy's mom!
她去片场找他
She's visiting him on set.
而且她长得都没想象中好看
Ah, and she's not even that cute.
等我们上天堂 我一定不原谅你
I am gonna be so mad at you in heaven.
你觉得我会上天堂吗
You think I'm going to heaven?
她居然觉得我会上天堂
She thinks I'm going to heaven.
飞机太重了 我们得丢掉一些重量
Plane's too heavy. We gotta drop some weight.
我就知道在卡车休息站的时候 不该吃那薯条
I knew those curly fries at the truck stop were a mistake,
可是他们那里也没有卖健康的其他选择啊
but they didn't offer a healthy alternative.
-拿着这个 -什么
- Hold this. - What? Ohh!
邋遢哥 天空是在这边
Hey, Sloppy, the sky is that way!
我也喜欢这个
I like this, too.
必须得丢掉行李箱
This suitcase has gotta go.
不行 我所有的衣服都在里面
No, all my clothes are in there.
我们所有的钱 我们的信用卡
All of our money! Our credit card!
那么小的一个箱子
There is no way that that one tiny suitcase
怎么可能给你飞机造成那么大的问题
is causing all these problems with your plane.
好吧 可能是我打包太多东西了
Very well, perhaps I overpacked.
上啤酒
Beer me.
上菜
Pick up!
除非你对"上"有意见
Unless that's a huge problem for you.
够了
That's it.
我要对你说我当年
I'm gonna tell you the same thing
对波头鹰餐厅
that I told Pooters
要给制服加上裤子时说的话
when they added pants to the uniform.
老娘不干了
I quit.
你不干了吗
You quit?
不不不不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
你是被炒了
You're fired.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah!
因为我是个"坏"女服务员吗
Have I been a bad waitress?
最坏最调皮的那个
The naughtiest.
他们不会就这么在餐厅里做爱吧
Uh, they're not gonna have sex in a restaurant, are they?
这也不会是第一次了
Well, it wouldn't be the first time.
连第八次都不是了
Hell, it wouldn't be the eighth time.
"上"菜啦 奥列格
Pick up, Oleg.
是的 兄弟 真要开"干"啦
Oh, yeah, man. This is happening.
我就是那时候娶了我高中的女朋友
And that's when I married my high school sweetheart.
她当时还在读高中 而我38岁了
Well, she was in high school. I was 38.
又一个妙极了的故事啊 邋遢哥
Another terrific story, Sloppy.
差点就让我忘了我们没钱
Almost makes me forget we have no money,
没衣服 而且这趟旅程连里程数都换不到
no clothes, and we're getting zero mileage for this flight.
塞翁失马焉知非福
Silver Linings Playbook, though.
小兰迪又更新了
Little Randy update.
麦克斯 我不在乎要多贵
Max, I don't care how expensive it is.
我们回去后你必须得去做心理治疗
You are going to therapy when we get back.
我们在奥斯丁 德克萨斯州拍摄的第一天
Well, that's a wrap on the first day of filming
就到此结束啦
here in Austin, Texas.
或者用当地人的话来说
Or as they say around these parts,
别德惹州人
don't Tess with Mexas.
还有被蝎子蛰后别喝酒
Don't drink on a scorpion bite.
他说得没错啊
The man ain't wrong.
等等 所以兰迪不在洛杉矶吗
Wait, so Randy's not in Los Angeles?
他是在德州
He's in Texas.
麦克斯 你真是个蹩脚的跟踪狂
Wow, you're a bad stalker, Max.
邋遢哥 随便左转还右转
Sloppy, hang a Ralph or a Louie.
转哪边能去德州就转哪边
Whatever gets us to Texas.
我邋遢平生有两件事不做
Eh, there's two things that Slop won't do.
告知相关单位我的飞行模式
Alert the proper authorities of my flight pattern
以及踏进德克萨斯州
or step foot in Texas.
你们得自己去了
You need to make your own way there.
我在这里放你们下 我刚好也得去嘘嘘
I'll drop you here. I gotta whiz anyway.
这里放我们下
Ah! Drop us here?
嘘嘘 这是什么意思
Whiz? What does that mean?
我想他的意思是我这个月
Uh, I think it means I'm jumping out
要跳第二次机了
of another plane this month.
告诉你啊 我好想念餐厅啊
You know what? I miss the diner.